traveling somewhere do you have a travel
insurance
well worry not the Royal Insurance
Corporation of Bhutan has introduced a
comprehensive domestic travel insurance
scheme for all your travel needs within
Burton the domestic travel insurance
covers travel by passenger buses taxis
and private cars including two wheelers
the domestic travel insurance also
covers travel in Indian states of Assam
and West Bengal come to think of it it
is as cheap as a packet of Douma the
domestic travel insurance covers life
risk worth 30,000 50,000 and 100,000
ultram for a one time premium of fifteen
twenty-five and fifty new trim
respectively the domestic travel
insurance covers single trip and expires
as soon as you reach your declared
destination in an unfortunate event the
insurance covers death or disability due
to the accident to claim the insurance
you should immediately inform in writing
to our nearest branch office the claim
will have to be made within one month
after the accident insure yourself while
traveling within bhutan travel without
worry
[Music]